No one disappears without a trace.
Missing is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Will Merrick.
When her mother disappears while on vacation in Colombia with her new boyfriend,
June’s search for answers is hindered by international red tape.
Stuck thousands of miles away in Los Angeles, June creatively uses all the latest
technology at her fingertips to try and find her before it’s too late.
But as she digs deeper, her digital sleuthing
raises more questions than answers...
and when June unravels secrets about her mom, she
discovers that she never really knew her at all.
June, played by Storm Reid.
Javi, played by Joaquim de Almeida.
Kevin, played by Ken Leung.
Heather, played by Amy Landecker.
Agent Park, played by Daniel Henney.
Grace, played by Nia Long.
Missing is a 2023 American screenlife mystery thriller film written and directed by Will Merrick and Nick Johnson (in their feature
directorial debuts) from a story by Sev Ohanian and Aneesh Chaganty, who also produced the film with Natalie Qasabian.
The film is a standalone film in the universe of Searching (2018).
It stars Storm Reid, Joaquim de Almeida, Ken Leung, Amy
Landecker, Daniel Henney, and Nia Long.
Its plot follows June Allen, a teenager who tries to find her missing mother
after she disappears on vacation in Colombia with her new boyfriend.
An anthology sequel to Searching was announced in 2019, with Merrick and Johnson, who edited
the first film, signing on to make their directorial debuts in January 2021.
Reid and Long joined the cast in the spring of 2021, and filming took place in Los
Angeles from March to May that year after delays due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
Missing also serves as a spiritual sequel to Run (2020), directed by Searching director Chaganty
and edited by Merrick and Johnson, confirming the fates of that film's characters.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed $48 million at the box office.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, amateur
detective, fbi, detective story, sequel.
The tone is intense and emotional and thought_provoking.